[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 15 + 1?",
        "options": [
            21,
            14,
            16,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 1 + 14?",
        "options": [
            16,
            20,
            15,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 28 + 16?",
        "options": [
            49,
            42,
            44,
            47
        ],
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 1 + 1?",
        "options": [
            7,
            2,
            4,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 17 + 11?",
        "options": [
            28,
            26,
            30,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 22 + 18?",
        "options": [
            40,
            43,
            36,
            39
        ],
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 30 + 3?",
        "options": [
            36,
            32,
            33,
            34
        ],
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 23 + 1?",
        "options": [
            24,
            23,
            22,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 27 + 5?",
        "options": [
            33,
            34,
            32,
            31
        ],
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 14 + 7?",
        "options": [
            16,
            23,
            19,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 19 + 11?",
        "options": [
            34,
            35,
            30,
            33
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 13 + 9?",
        "options": [
            25,
            22,
            23,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 7 + 19?",
        "options": [
            30,
            28,
            26,
            24
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 28 + 14?",
        "options": [
            42,
            41,
            45,
            37
        ],
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 22 + 4?",
        "options": [
            25,
            28,
            26,
            24
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 + 9?",
        "options": [
            21,
            24,
            20,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 25 + 7?",
        "options": [
            33,
            36,
            27,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 27 + 20?",
        "options": [
            46,
            42,
            50,
            47
        ],
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 + 12?",
        "options": [
            12,
            16,
            17,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 19 + 16?",
        "options": [
            35,
            30,
            39,
            38
        ],
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 49 + 31?",
        "options": [
            83,
            77,
            75,
            80
        ],
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 66 + 21?",
        "options": [
            87,
            84,
            93,
            86
        ],
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 46 + 35?",
        "options": [
            73,
            81,
            79,
            80
        ],
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 67 + 33?",
        "options": [
            101,
            100,
            109,
            91
        ],
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 42 + 22?",
        "options": [
            62,
            64,
            58,
            65
        ],
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 70 + 37?",
        "options": [
            114,
            102,
            107,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 35 + 36?",
        "options": [
            65,
            71,
            78,
            69
        ],
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 68 + 36?",
        "options": [
            108,
            98,
            104,
            114
        ],
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 39 + 49?",
        "options": [
            88,
            93,
            96,
            89
        ],
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 62 + 30?",
        "options": [
            92,
            96,
            97,
            87
        ],
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 70 + 40?",
        "options": [
            119,
            110,
            103,
            107
        ],
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 61 + 28?",
        "options": [
            87,
            94,
            89,
            88
        ],
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 56 + 29?",
        "options": [
            84,
            86,
            87,
            85
        ],
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 58 + 29?",
        "options": [
            79,
            87,
            90,
            89
        ],
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 54 + 28?",
        "options": [
            80,
            86,
            89,
            82
        ],
        "answer": 82
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 56 + 27?",
        "options": [
            81,
            83,
            80,
            90
        ],
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 39 + 43?",
        "options": [
            90,
            89,
            77,
            82
        ],
        "answer": 82
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 47 + 36?",
        "options": [
            91,
            83,
            81,
            87
        ],
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 56 + 44?",
        "options": [
            93,
            108,
            105,
            100
        ],
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 36 + 48?",
        "options": [
            87,
            84,
            79,
            80
        ],
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 92 + 60?",
        "options": [
            159,
            152,
            139,
            148
        ],
        "answer": 152
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 73 + 99?",
        "options": [
            172,
            162,
            188,
            159
        ],
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 101 + 61?",
        "options": [
            158,
            154,
            162,
            173
        ],
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 91 + 63?",
        "options": [
            160,
            144,
            157,
            154
        ],
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 114 + 68?",
        "options": [
            199,
            191,
            169,
            182
        ],
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 76 + 92?",
        "options": [
            166,
            168,
            184,
            172
        ],
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 83 + 82?",
        "options": [
            155,
            154,
            170,
            165
        ],
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 82 + 63?",
        "options": [
            133,
            156,
            144,
            145
        ],
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 106 + 67?",
        "options": [
            156,
            173,
            177,
            159
        ],
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 77 + 96?",
        "options": [
            183,
            170,
            167,
            173
        ],
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 84 + 70?",
        "options": [
            166,
            139,
            169,
            154
        ],
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 78 + 72?",
        "options": [
            152,
            143,
            150,
            147
        ],
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 94 + 98?",
        "options": [
            192,
            185,
            184,
            199
        ],
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 98 + 87?",
        "options": [
            176,
            185,
            197,
            178
        ],
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 75 + 81?",
        "options": [
            142,
            143,
            160,
            156
        ],
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 90 + 71?",
        "options": [
            161,
            172,
            146,
            154
        ],
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 79 + 75?",
        "options": [
            149,
            154,
            155,
            144
        ],
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 115 + 80?",
        "options": [
            195,
            214,
            186,
            179
        ],
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 116 + 85?",
        "options": [
            201,
            193,
            188,
            221
        ],
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "category": "Addition",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 79 + 100?",
        "options": [
            179,
            164,
            180,
            174
        ],
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 7 - 3?",
        "options": [
            4,
            7,
            6,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 11 - 10?",
        "options": [
            2,
            6,
            5,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 9 - 3?",
        "options": [
            2,
            8,
            10,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 5 - 2?",
        "options": [
            3,
            8,
            7,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 - 5?",
        "options": [
            3,
            4,
            2,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 20 - 6?",
        "options": [
            10,
            11,
            14,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 9 - 5?",
        "options": [
            0,
            6,
            4,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 - 1?",
        "options": [
            16,
            11,
            9,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 19 - 11?",
        "options": [
            8,
            12,
            4,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 - 3?",
        "options": [
            8,
            5,
            6,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 29 - 3?",
        "options": [
            22,
            30,
            28,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 - 1?",
        "options": [
            8,
            5,
            3,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 - 11?",
        "options": [
            4,
            3,
            2,
            1
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 23 - 15?",
        "options": [
            11,
            6,
            8,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 7 - 5?",
        "options": [
            2,
            7,
            1,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 14 - 13?",
        "options": [
            6,
            1,
            3,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 30 - 5?",
        "options": [
            27,
            30,
            25,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 5 - 1?",
        "options": [
            0,
            1,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 10 - 8?",
        "options": [
            1,
            4,
            5,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 24 - 5?",
        "options": [
            23,
            24,
            19,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 50 - 35?",
        "options": [
            10,
            15,
            18,
            16
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 55 - 39?",
        "options": [
            16,
            17,
            18,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 49 - 29?",
        "options": [
            20,
            22,
            18,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 32 - 21?",
        "options": [
            11,
            7,
            16,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 57 - 28?",
        "options": [
            28,
            33,
            30,
            29
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 39 - 24?",
        "options": [
            12,
            20,
            15,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 40 - 35?",
        "options": [
            5,
            8,
            6,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 45 - 23?",
        "options": [
            20,
            21,
            22,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 31 - 29?",
        "options": [
            2,
            7,
            3,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 47 - 40?",
        "options": [
            7,
            3,
            10,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 41 - 37?",
        "options": [
            9,
            4,
            2,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 37 - 32?",
        "options": [
            9,
            5,
            6,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 70 - 44?",
        "options": [
            26,
            23,
            29,
            24
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 38 - 24?",
        "options": [
            9,
            16,
            14,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 64 - 30?",
        "options": [
            37,
            34,
            32,
            29
        ],
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 35 - 27?",
        "options": [
            5,
            10,
            8,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 52 - 24?",
        "options": [
            30,
            28,
            24,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 35 - 24?",
        "options": [
            12,
            16,
            11,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 59 - 30?",
        "options": [
            29,
            26,
            27,
            34
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 43 - 37?",
        "options": [
            4,
            7,
            9,
            6
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 133 - 62?",
        "options": [
            71,
            68,
            77,
            64
        ],
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 81 - 68?",
        "options": [
            18,
            17,
            15,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 143 - 87?",
        "options": [
            61,
            56,
            54,
            55
        ],
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 90 - 89?",
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            5,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 137 - 54?",
        "options": [
            83,
            87,
            90,
            85
        ],
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 83 - 57?",
        "options": [
            29,
            26,
            27,
            24
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 134 - 108?",
        "options": [
            31,
            24,
            25,
            26
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 126 - 71?",
        "options": [
            55,
            50,
            59,
            60
        ],
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 88 - 86?",
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            0,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 101 - 80?",
        "options": [
            18,
            21,
            20,
            16
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 140 - 137?",
        "options": [
            6,
            3,
            7,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 102 - 95?",
        "options": [
            11,
            7,
            8,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 96 - 79?",
        "options": [
            18,
            17,
            21,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 73 - 69?",
        "options": [
            3,
            1,
            6,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 109 - 58?",
        "options": [
            51,
            49,
            50,
            48
        ],
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 96 - 87?",
        "options": [
            13,
            4,
            8,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 80 - 74?",
        "options": [
            8,
            5,
            6,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 93 - 67?",
        "options": [
            21,
            27,
            26,
            28
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 71 - 59?",
        "options": [
            17,
            11,
            12,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "category": "Subtraction",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 117 - 97?",
        "options": [
            20,
            22,
            15,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 2?",
        "options": [
            15,
            10,
            14,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 5?",
        "options": [
            26,
            31,
            27,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            12,
            15,
            14,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 9?",
        "options": [
            15,
            22,
            23,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 10?",
        "options": [
            99,
            110,
            119,
            116
        ],
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 12?",
        "options": [
            69,
            76,
            67,
            72
        ],
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 10?",
        "options": [
            66,
            65,
            62,
            60
        ],
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 6?",
        "options": [
            40,
            39,
            42,
            46
        ],
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 4?",
        "options": [
            31,
            33,
            28,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 5?",
        "options": [
            55,
            60,
            51,
            52
        ],
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 10?",
        "options": [
            30,
            28,
            33,
            35
        ],
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 5?",
        "options": [
            51,
            50,
            46,
            54
        ],
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 10?",
        "options": [
            66,
            70,
            72,
            67
        ],
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 11?",
        "options": [
            23,
            22,
            26,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 12?",
        "options": [
            151,
            137,
            144,
            152
        ],
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 4?",
        "options": [
            32,
            36,
            39,
            38
        ],
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 10?",
        "options": [
            46,
            45,
            54,
            50
        ],
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 4?",
        "options": [
            12,
            14,
            16,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 3?",
        "options": [
            20,
            19,
            22,
            24
        ],
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 5?",
        "options": [
            44,
            35,
            40,
            37
        ],
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 21?",
        "options": [
            402,
            357,
            356,
            378
        ],
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 15?",
        "options": [
            203,
            199,
            210,
            195
        ],
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 20?",
        "options": [
            393,
            366,
            352,
            380
        ],
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 17?",
        "options": [
            297,
            269,
            310,
            289
        ],
        "answer": 289
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 17?",
        "options": [
            273,
            255,
            275,
            233
        ],
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 20?",
        "options": [
            260,
            245,
            253,
            241
        ],
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 16?",
        "options": [
            278,
            284,
            290,
            288
        ],
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 17?",
        "options": [
            297,
            323,
            307,
            318
        ],
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 19?",
        "options": [
            285,
            306,
            291,
            302
        ],
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 13?",
        "options": [
            273,
            284,
            282,
            278
        ],
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 16?",
        "options": [
            298,
            277,
            272,
            251
        ],
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 14?",
        "options": [
            250,
            260,
            238,
            235
        ],
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 15?",
        "options": [
            200,
            195,
            183,
            186
        ],
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 19?",
        "options": [
            368,
            327,
            342,
            337
        ],
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 13?",
        "options": [
            169,
            178,
            158,
            183
        ],
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 14?",
        "options": [
            209,
            238,
            224,
            227
        ],
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 13?",
        "options": [
            223,
            247,
            224,
            233
        ],
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 17?",
        "options": [
            240,
            221,
            243,
            220
        ],
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 19?",
        "options": [
            351,
            392,
            361,
            348
        ],
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 20?",
        "options": [
            315,
            295,
            316,
            300
        ],
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 30?",
        "options": [
            856,
            718,
            740,
            780
        ],
        "answer": 780
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 25?",
        "options": [
            665,
            676,
            648,
            675
        ],
        "answer": 675
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 24?",
        "options": [
            702,
            701,
            744,
            695
        ],
        "answer": 744
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 29?",
        "options": [
            664,
            699,
            766,
            725
        ],
        "answer": 725
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 23?",
        "options": [
            657,
            690,
            637,
            708
        ],
        "answer": 690
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 35 \u00d7 27?",
        "options": [
            942,
            867,
            988,
            945
        ],
        "answer": 945
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 33 \u00d7 24?",
        "options": [
            859,
            811,
            766,
            792
        ],
        "answer": 792
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 23?",
        "options": [
            730,
            668,
            667,
            635
        ],
        "answer": 667
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 33?",
        "options": [
            957,
            1017,
            921,
            984
        ],
        "answer": 957
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 29?",
        "options": [
            899,
            903,
            977,
            842
        ],
        "answer": 899
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 35 \u00d7 34?",
        "options": [
            1207,
            1190,
            1300,
            1261
        ],
        "answer": 1190
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 35 \u00d7 35?",
        "options": [
            1263,
            1296,
            1145,
            1225
        ],
        "answer": 1225
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 32?",
        "options": [
            818,
            894,
            896,
            930
        ],
        "answer": 896
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 32?",
        "options": [
            699,
            693,
            736,
            761
        ],
        "answer": 736
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 28?",
        "options": [
            728,
            667,
            738,
            701
        ],
        "answer": 728
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 34?",
        "options": [
            807,
            741,
            784,
            782
        ],
        "answer": 782
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 30?",
        "options": [
            720,
            767,
            772,
            665
        ],
        "answer": 720
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 29?",
        "options": [
            841,
            839,
            799,
            877
        ],
        "answer": 841
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 30?",
        "options": [
            690,
            677,
            689,
            714
        ],
        "answer": 690
    },
    {
        "id": 180,
        "category": "Multiplication",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 23?",
        "options": [
            742,
            705,
            713,
            775
        ],
        "answer": 713
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 7?",
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            5,
            8
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 81 \u00f7 9?",
        "options": [
            12,
            9,
            10,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 183,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 12?",
        "options": [
            1,
            7,
            3,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 184,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 16 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            7,
            12,
            8,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 185,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 132 \u00f7 12?",
        "options": [
            14,
            8,
            10,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 108 \u00f7 9?",
        "options": [
            16,
            12,
            9,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "id": 187,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            13,
            8,
            10,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "id": 188,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 77 \u00f7 11?",
        "options": [
            7,
            10,
            6,
            11
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 189,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 6?",
        "options": [
            8,
            13,
            9,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 190,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 84 \u00f7 12?",
        "options": [
            9,
            7,
            8,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 191,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 9?",
        "options": [
            9,
            4,
            8,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 192,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 8?",
        "options": [
            6,
            5,
            10,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 193,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            0,
            5,
            6,
            2
        ],
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 194,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 99 \u00f7 9?",
        "options": [
            11,
            12,
            9,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 195,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 4?",
        "options": [
            5,
            2,
            1,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 196,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 8 \u00f7 2?",
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            0,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 197,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 77 \u00f7 7?",
        "options": [
            9,
            11,
            15,
            13
        ],
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "id": 198,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 64 \u00f7 8?",
        "options": [
            13,
            7,
            8,
            5
        ],
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "id": 199,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 11?",
        "options": [
            0,
            4,
            7,
            3
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 200,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 11?",
        "options": [
            5,
            1,
            2,
            7
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 201,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 399 \u00f7 21?",
        "options": [
            17,
            19,
            14,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 202,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 294 \u00f7 21?",
        "options": [
            11,
            13,
            12,
            14
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 203,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 247 \u00f7 19?",
        "options": [
            12,
            10,
            13,
            16
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 204,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 238 \u00f7 17?",
        "options": [
            9,
            14,
            13,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 205,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 196 \u00f7 14?",
        "options": [
            14,
            16,
            11,
            12
        ],
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "id": 206,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 285 \u00f7 19?",
        "options": [
            15,
            19,
            17,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 207,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 270 \u00f7 18?",
        "options": [
            20,
            19,
            15,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 208,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 288 \u00f7 16?",
        "options": [
            23,
            19,
            20,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "id": 209,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 399 \u00f7 19?",
        "options": [
            24,
            23,
            21,
            18
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 210,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 266 \u00f7 14?",
        "options": [
            19,
            18,
            16,
            17
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 211,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 285 \u00f7 15?",
        "options": [
            14,
            21,
            18,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "id": 212,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 300 \u00f7 15?",
        "options": [
            15,
            23,
            22,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 213,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 360 \u00f7 20?",
        "options": [
            20,
            17,
            18,
            15
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "id": 214,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 272 \u00f7 16?",
        "options": [
            17,
            22,
            16,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 215,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 378 \u00f7 18?",
        "options": [
            19,
            21,
            22,
            23
        ],
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "id": 216,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 210 \u00f7 14?",
        "options": [
            14,
            20,
            15,
            10
        ],
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "id": 217,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 306 \u00f7 17?",
        "options": [
            16,
            18,
            21,
            20
        ],
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "id": 218,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 289 \u00f7 17?",
        "options": [
            18,
            21,
            17,
            19
        ],
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "id": 219,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 182 \u00f7 14?",
        "options": [
            10,
            12,
            13,
            9
        ],
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "id": 220,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Medium",
        "question": "What is 400 \u00f7 20?",
        "options": [
            20,
            24,
            17,
            23
        ],
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "id": 221,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 986 \u00f7 29?",
        "options": [
            32,
            33,
            37,
            34
        ],
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "id": 222,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 806 \u00f7 31?",
        "options": [
            25,
            24,
            26,
            21
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 223,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 1190 \u00f7 35?",
        "options": [
            35,
            38,
            32,
            34
        ],
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "id": 224,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 736 \u00f7 23?",
        "options": [
            32,
            27,
            33,
            31
        ],
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "id": 225,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 1155 \u00f7 35?",
        "options": [
            38,
            30,
            28,
            33
        ],
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "id": 226,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 918 \u00f7 34?",
        "options": [
            30,
            22,
            27,
            31
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "id": 227,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 841 \u00f7 29?",
        "options": [
            29,
            28,
            33,
            31
        ],
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "id": 228,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 675 \u00f7 25?",
        "options": [
            26,
            31,
            27,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "id": 229,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 832 \u00f7 26?",
        "options": [
            32,
            27,
            30,
            34
        ],
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "id": 230,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 875 \u00f7 35?",
        "options": [
            29,
            25,
            21,
            23
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 231,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 700 \u00f7 28?",
        "options": [
            28,
            21,
            29,
            25
        ],
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "id": 232,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 980 \u00f7 28?",
        "options": [
            40,
            35,
            36,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "id": 233,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 924 \u00f7 28?",
        "options": [
            36,
            28,
            33,
            30
        ],
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "id": 234,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 910 \u00f7 26?",
        "options": [
            31,
            33,
            34,
            35
        ],
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "id": 235,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 713 \u00f7 31?",
        "options": [
            26,
            27,
            23,
            22
        ],
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "id": 236,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 676 \u00f7 26?",
        "options": [
            26,
            25,
            28,
            31
        ],
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "id": 237,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 1088 \u00f7 34?",
        "options": [
            37,
            32,
            33,
            27
        ],
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "id": 238,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 812 \u00f7 29?",
        "options": [
            28,
            31,
            32,
            33
        ],
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "id": 239,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 792 \u00f7 24?",
        "options": [
            32,
            30,
            36,
            33
        ],
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "id": 240,
        "category": "Division",
        "difficulty": "Difficult",
        "question": "What is 945 \u00f7 27?",
        "options": [
            33,
            38,
            35,
            32
        ],
        "answer": 35
    }
]